http://0blog.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Our basic privacy policy is simple. We will not rent, sell, or share personal information that we collect about you.
Toivo Lainevool's Random Thoughts takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it.
Routine Information Collection
All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.
Cookies and Web Beacons
Where necessary, Toivo Lainevool's Random Thoughts uses cookies to store information about a visitor's preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.
Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.
Controlling Your Privacy
Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.
Special Note About Google Advertising
Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google's cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google's own privacy policies.
Contact Information
Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to tlainevool@gmail.com for further clarification.
This entry was posted
on Saturday, April 5th, 2008 at 11:17 am						and is filed under All.
You can follow any responses to this entry through the RSS 2.0 feed.
You can leave a response, or trackback from your own site.
Leave a Reply
Name
Mail (will not be published)
Website
Starts with Zero.
Tech, movies, music, food and other random leakage from Toivo "Deutsch" Lainevool's Brain.
Fight Splog! Eliminate Spam Blogs.
Who Has the Best Pool in Las Vegas?
